<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>The Nest Blog</title>
        <link>https://crystalwwj.github.io/the-nest/blog</link>
        <description>The Nest Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent changes...]]></title>
            <link>https://crystalwwj.github.io/the-nest/blog/first-job-switch</link>
            <guid>first-job-switch</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Recently, I've decided to quit my current job and join another renowned cybersecurity company. It wasn't exactly planned as I was only curious about what the position, the company, and the people there were like. I wasn't some sort of disgruntled employee looking for new opportunities. Well, I was looking at the opportunity, of course, but rather than being pushed forward by some grudge I was more interested in exploring the landscape of the cybersecurity industry. I'm still rather fresh to the field with merely three years of exposure, if you count undergrad courses and projects, and still have so much ahead to discover.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently, I&#x27;ve decided to quit my current job and join another renowned cybersecurity company. It wasn&#x27;t exactly planned as I was only curious about what the position, the company, and the people there were like. I wasn&#x27;t some sort of disgruntled employee looking for new opportunities. Well, I <em>was</em> looking at the opportunity, of course, but rather than being pushed forward by some grudge I was more interested in exploring the landscape of the cybersecurity industry. I&#x27;m still rather fresh to the field with merely three years of exposure, if you count undergrad courses and projects, and still have so much ahead to discover. </p><p>I&#x27;m not a naturally curious person. Well, maybe I&#x27;m interested in learning about lots of stuff, but that&#x27;s just &#x27;whoa cool, how does it work&#x27; level of interest, not &#x27;I love this gonna deep dive&#x27; level of passion. To be honest with myself, I don&#x27;t think I ever had a passion. When I do things it mostly started off a whiz, and then I try to stick to it because I don&#x27;t like the feeling of giving up. Unless I hate it already, I try to do my best and get the most out of it. So most things I do for a while or do well, it&#x27;s probably out of perserverence rather than passion. And that&#x27;s the worst thing about me. I can&#x27;t seem to find something that hits different, that rings a bell in my ears like how fate calls upon the destined. I&#x27;ve been searching and trying out stuff, but nothing ever worked out. Finally I settled on what my father told me: something that I might not love but will always have some fun in. That&#x27;s how cybersecurity came along. Something I won&#x27;t call my passion but is cool enough to retain my interest.</p><p>So, yeah. The job switch came unexpected. To my family, to my colleagues, and to me, too.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grand Opening!]]></title>
            <link>https://crystalwwj.github.io/the-nest/blog/grand-opening</link>
            <guid>grand-opening</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hi there! This is the very first blog post of The Nest.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hi there! This is the very first blog post of The Nest.</p><p>I&#x27;ve been thinking about setting up a personal website so that I can access my notes from anywhere. I love my note taking apps but sometimes it&#x27;s annoying that I only have my valuable stuff on my working computer. Besides, my partner and I wanted to start keeping docs on somewhere other than Google Drive, both as motivation to learn more stuff and keep record of our progress.</p><p>Anyway, this website is probably going to contain random posts and notes for all kinds of stuff. I&#x27;ll mainly work on cybersecurity and things I recently encountered on work, while Steven might be documenting some of his own studies. We hope to also continue our language learning endeavors. And probably some travel blogs or rambles.</p><p>That&#x27;s it for now!</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>